let quiz   =[
    {question: "A cone is 8.4 cm high and the radius of its base is 2.1 cm. It is melted and recast into a shape. The radius of the sphere is",
option:[
    "4.2 cm",
    "2.1 cm",
    "2.4 cm",
    "1.6 cm",

],
answer:2, 
},

{
    question: "The length of the longest pole that can be put in a room of dimension(10 m X 10 m X5 m)" ,
option:[
    "15 m",
    "16 m",
    "10 m",
    "12 m",


],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "The radii of two cylinders are in the ratio of 2:3 and their heights are in the ratio of 5:3. The ratio of their volumes is",
option:[
    "10:17",
    "20:37",
    "20:27",
    "10:15",


],
answer:3, 
},
{question: "The radius of a hemispherical balloon increases from 6 cm to 12 cm as air is being pumped into it. the ratios of the surface areas of the balloon in two cases is ",
option:[
    "1:4",
    "2:4",
    "3:4",
    "7:7",

],
answer:1, 
},

{
    question: "Two parallelograms are on equal bases and the same parallels. The ratio of their areas is",
option:[
    "1:1",
    "2:1",
    "2:4",
    "3:4",

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "If a triangle and a parallelogram are on the same base and between same parallels,then the ratio of the area of the triangle to the area of the triangle to the area of parallelogram is",
option:[
    "3:4",
    "2:3",
    "1:2",
    "2:1",
],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "A chord is at a distance of 8 cm from the centre of a circle of radius 17 cm. The length of the chord is",
option:[
    "25 cm",
    "12.5 cm",
    "9 cm",
    "30 cm",

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "The radius of a circle is 13 cm and the length of one of its chords is 10 cm. The distance of the chord from the centre is" ,
option:[
    " 12 cm",
    "11.5 cm",
    "12.5 cm",
    "11",


],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "When p(x) is divided by 'ax-b', then the remainder is",
option:[
    "p(a+b)",
    "p(a/b)",
    "p(-b/a)",
    "p(b/a)",

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "Which of the following can not be the empirical probability of an event?",
option:[
    "2/3",
    "3/2",
    0,
    1,

    
],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "The probability that a number selected at random from the numbers 1,2,3,...,15 is a multiple of 4 is",
option:[
    "4/15",
    "2/15",
    "1/5",
    "1/3",

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "The median of the data '78,56,22,34,45,54,39,68,54,84' is",
option:[
    45,
    49.5,
    54,
    56,

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "The construction of the triangle ABC is possible if it is given 'BC=4 cm' '<c = 60 degree' and the diffence of AB and AC is",
option:[
    "3.5 cm",
    "4.5 cm",
    "3 cm",
    "2.5 cm",

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "If a,b and c are the lkengths of three sides of a triangle,then:",
option:[
    "a+b>c",
    "a-b>c",
    "a+b=c",    
    "a-b=c",

],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "When a die is throw, the probability of getting an odd number less than 4 is",
option:[
    "1/6",
    "1/3",
    "1/2",
    "1/4",

],
answer:2, 
}]